http://tagassoc.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - TAG Associates About UsOur HeritageOur PeopleWho We ServeOur ServicesPortfolio ManagementApproach to AlternativesFamily OfficePerspectives TAG Associates LLC: Financial Privacy NoticeTAG Associates LLC is a registered investment adviser with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) under the Investment Adviser Act of 1940. The SEC requires registered investment advisers to disclose how we treat nonpublic information. The following is a description of our policies regarding disclosure of nonpublic personal information that you provide to TAG.We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:Information we receive from you directly (including name, address, income and other financial-related information).Data about your transactions with us (such as the types of investments you have made and your account status).Information about you provided to us from third parties pursuant to your authorization. We do not disclose any information, including but not limited to nonpublic information listed above, about our clients or former clients to anyone, except as required by law (such as to respond to a subpoena or to prevent fraud), as necessary in order to administer and service clients’ accounts, or as authorized by such clients or former clients.We restrict access to nonpublic information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your nonpublic personal information.About UsOur HeritageOur PeopleWho We ServeOur ServicesOur Services OverviewPortfolio ManagementApproach to AlternativesFamily OfficePerspectives
